SABER EL ADRAOUI

IT TECHNICIAN & MULTIMEDIA DEVELOPER



CONTACT

076-252-6669

saber.adraoui@gmail.com

Tangier, Morocco

saberea.live

SKILLS

- Web Design
- Web Development
- · Design Thinking
- Customer Service
- Front End Coding
- · Problem-Solving
- IT Specialist
- Strong Communication
- · Flexibility and Creativity
- Self-taught

EDUCATION

TECHNICAL DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER MAINTENANCE AND SUPPORT AND NETWORKS

ISMONTIC / Tangier 2016 - 2018

TECHNICAL DIPLOMA IN MULTIMEDIA DEVELOPMENT

ISMONTIC / Tangier

2019 - 2021

LANGUAGES

ARABIC

Native

ENGLISH

Fluent

FRENSH

Intermediate

SPANISH

Beginner

PROFILE

Competent and very flexible IT Specialist with 2 years of professional experience highly motivated to explore and acquire more knowledge in the IT Field. Recently graduated from the institute of technology with a specialization in IT and network technical support and my second specialization in multimedia development during my training and work experience I acquired a lot of expertise in graphic design, web development, network management, and computer and network support.

EXPERIENCE

WEBMASTER

Sahih Business

Jan 2022 - Oct 2022

- Create, design, enhance, update and maintain the website according to the client's objectives and requirements in order to meet the web industry standards.
- Troubleshoot issues with websites and fixed scripting and use issues.
- redesign apps via adding a new information architecture schema and content strategy, as well as the design of sketches, flow diagrams, wireframes, mock-ups and UI/UX Designs.
- Implemented custom HTML5 code into CMS system based on client needs (WordPress, Codelgniter, Laravel).

IT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

Planet Computer

Oct 2019 - Jan 2020

- Maintained office & clients PCs, networks, and mobile devices.
- Set up PCs, projectors, and microphones for use in video conferencing rooms.
- Established, repaired, and optimized networks by installing wiring, cabling, and devices.
- Performed necessary maintenance to support network availability.
- Troubleshot and resolved LAN/WAN connectivity issues.

IT HARDWARE TECHNICIAN

Panier Media

Oct 2018 - Mar 2019

- · Maintained technology equipment performance by configuring, and repairing hardware.
- Demonstrated strong knowledge of all types of electrical components, operations, specifications, and proper testing methods including software and hardware.
- Followed up with clients to verify optimal customer satisfaction following support engagement and problem resolution
- Patched & update software to eliminate security problems and protect data.

CERTIFICATIONS

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN

freeCodeCamp Apr 2022

IT ESSENTIALS: PC HARDWARE AND SOFTWARE

Cisco

Sep 2017